[
  {
    "name": "Capacitor Lab",
    "id": "capacitor-lab",
    "exec": "java -jar \/opt\/phet\/physics\/capacitor-lab_en.jar",
    "type": "apps",
    "keywords": [
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "description": "Explore how a capacitor works! Change the size of the plates and add a dielectric to see how it affects capacitance. Change the voltage and see charges built up on the plates. Shows the electric field in the capacitor. Measure voltage and electric field.",
    "manuals": [
      {
        "title": "Using PhET in Electricity Unit",
        "src": "pdf-reader /var/www/manuals\/electricity-unit.pdf"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Circuit Construction Kit (DC Only)",
    "id": "circuit-construction- kit",
    "exec": "java -jar \/opt\/phet\/physics\/circuit-construction-kit-dc_en.jar",
    "type": "apps",
    "keywords": [
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "description": "An electronics kit in your computer! Build circuits with resistors, light bulbs, batteries, and switches. Take measurements with the realistic ammeter and voltmeter. View the circuit as a schematic diagram, or switch to a life-like view.",
    "manuals": [
      {
        "title": "Introduction",
        "src": "pdf-reader /var/www/manuals\/circuit-directions.pdf"
      },
      {
        "title": "Series and Parallel",
        "src": "doc-reader /var/www/manuals\/circuit-series-parallel.doc"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Circuit Construction Kit (AC+DC)",
    "id": "circuit-construction- kit",
    "exec": "java -jar \/opt\/phet\/physics\/circuit-construction-kit-ac_en.jar",
    "type": "apps",
    "keywords": [
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "description": "This new version of the CCK adds capacitors, inductors and AC voltage sources to your toolbox! Now you can graph the current and voltage as a function of time.",
    "manuals": [
      {
        "title": "Introduction",
        "src": "pdf-reader /var/www/manuals\/circuit-directions.pdf"
      },
      {
        "title": "Series and Parallel",
        "src": "doc-reader /var/www/manuals\/circuit-series-parallel.doc"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Ohm's Law",
    "id": "ohms-law",
    "type": "videos",
    "keywords": [
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Battery-Resistor Circuit",
    "id": "battery-resistor",
    "type": "videos",
    "keywords": [
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "this is a__test__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "this"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "is"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "a_______"
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "Test",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "Sattar is __sattar__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "Sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "is"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "sattar"
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "Sattar",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "sattar__sattar__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "sattar_______"
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "sattar2",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [],
    "name": "asd",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [],
    "name": "asd",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "my name is __Mehra__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "my name is"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "Mehra"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "qwe",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [],
    "name": "sattar34",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "satar __satta__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "satar"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "satta"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "nikhil",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "satatr__sattar__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "satatr"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "sattar34356",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "",
        "questionCollection": [],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "sarsfghfdf",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "name": "Sample Quiz",
    "type": "quiz",
    "questions": [
      {
        "marks": 1,
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "__Nehru__ 's birthday is __Children__ 's day.",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "Nehru"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "'s"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "birthday"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "is"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "Children"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "'s"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "day."
          }
        ],
        "$$hashKey": "object:14"
      },
      {
        "marks": 1,
        "type": "multiple-options",
        "question": "What is your name of the country?",
        "options": [
          {
            "value": "India",
            "answer": true
          },
          {
            "value": "Pakistan",
            "answer": true
          },
          {
            "value": "America",
            "answer": false
          }
        ],
        "$$hashKey": "object:22"
      },
      {
        "marks": 1,
        "type": "match-the-following",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "Vinoth",
            "answer": "Kumar"
          },
          {
            "question": "This is my test Question. This is my test Question.",
            "answer": "This is my test Answer. This is my test Answer."
          },
          {
            "question": "Nikhil",
            "answer": "Test Match"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "sattar__sattar__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "",
        "questionCollection": [],
        "marks": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "",
        "questionCollection": [],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "sattar343667",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "sattar__sattar__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "shikpa",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "marks": 1,
        "type": "match-the-following",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "srujan",
            "answer": "kumar"
          },
          {
            "question": "sattar",
            "answer": "abdul"
          },
          {
            "question": "prateek",
            "answer": "richi"
          },
          {
            "question": "nalini k",
            "answer": "kanth"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "name": "rajinikant",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "marks": 1,
        "type": "match-the-following",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "abdul",
            "answer": "sattar"
          },
          {
            "question": "prateek",
            "answer": "richi"
          },
          {
            "question": "srujan",
            "answer": "bojjam"
          },
          {
            "question": "nailini",
            "answer": "kanth"
          }
        ]
      }
    ],
    "name": "whatever",
    "type": "quiz"
  },
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "kjsdabfkjbfjk__njcnfjkvbf__jksfjkvbfskjvkjsfb",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "kjsdabfkjbfjk"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "njcnfjkvbf"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "jksfjkvbfskjvkjsfb"
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "__jsfvm,s vfs mv____s,m cvm,scvm,vmfs c__ldjfnlvfsvfsmvfsmvfsjknvfjksv lms",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "jsfvm,s vfs mv"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "s,m cvm,scvm,vmfs c"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "ldjfnlvfsvfsmvfsmvfsjknvfjksv lms"
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      },
      {
        "type": "fill-the-blanks",
        "question": "jsncvjksbvkjsfbjkvbsfkbvfskvskjbvkj__jkvb dfjkv kdjf vfjkd__",
        "questionCollection": [
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": "jsncvjksbvkjsfbjkvbsfkbvfskvskjbvkj"
          },
          {
            "type": "answer",
            "value": "jkvb dfjkv kdjf vfjkd"
          },
          {
            "type": "question",
            "value": ""
          }
        ],
        "marks": 1
      }
    ],
    "name": "sjknvsknfv nsmdv mns vmns vmns",
    "type": "quiz"
  }
]
